[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":39178,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":47645,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":5023,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":52671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6052,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":58726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2551,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":61279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":66679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1051,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":67732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["1","0"],"rt":8856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":76589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":851,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":77442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2151,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":79595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 becau se 1 + 1  = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1479,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":81077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":82909,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":759,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":83670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first numb er, and  then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":85591,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":765,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":86357,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1820,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":88179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":667,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":88849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":90651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1235,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":91887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2153,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":94041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":727,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":94768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":96484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":597,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":97082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":12149,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":109233,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":15406,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":124642,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4465,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":129109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7- 0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1235,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":130345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":1718,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":132064,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":649,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":132715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6< /sub>? < br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1385,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":134101,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":821,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":134923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1492,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":136417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":746,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":137163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":139344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3751,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":143097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":16560,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":159658,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a g enerator  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":20980,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":180641,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":18513,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":199158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2314,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":201473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a g enerator  under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":12529,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":214003,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":3309,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":217314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a ge nerator  is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":12092,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":229408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1463,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":230873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3053,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":233928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1988,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":235918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10812,"trial_type":"i nstructi ons","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":246732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2419,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":249151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":908,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":250060,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2119,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":252179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1800,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":253979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2181,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":256161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":1686,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":257848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":260103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is  4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays that number.","response_history":["5. Becuase 1","5. Becuase ","5. Becuase","5. Becuas","5. Becua","5. Becu","5. Because 1+4-","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is <","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays tha","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays th","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays te same.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays t same.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays tha same.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays that same.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays thatsame.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays thatame.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays thatme.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays thate.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it s tays tha t.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays that .","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays that nu.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays that num.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays that numbe.","5. Because 1+4=5, and 5 is less than 9, it stays that number."],"rt":28855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":288960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. Because 8+4=12, and 12 > 9, we subtract 9 from 12 and get 3.","response_history":["3. Because 8+4 =","3. Because 8+4 ","3. Because 8+4=12, and 12 >9","3. Because 8+4=12, and 12 > 9, we subtract 9 from `12","3. Because 8+4=12, and 12 > 9, we subtract 9 from `1","3. Because 8+4=12, and 12 > 9, we subtract 9 from `","3. Because 8+4=12, and 12 > 9, we subtract 9 from 1","3. Beca use 8+4= 12, and 12 > 9, we subtract 9 from 12 and get 3."],"rt":14843,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":303805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, because like in +6 math, adding 0 to anything will give you that number back.","response_history":["0, because like in +6 math, adding 0 to anything will give you that number back."],"rt":52922,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":356729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5733,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":362465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is  the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2186,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":364652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2187,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":366843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. Because 6+3=9, which becomes 0.","response_history":["6. Because 6+3 ","6. Because 6+3=0","6. Because 6+3=9, which becoems 0","6. Because 6+3=9, which becoems ","6. Because 6+3=9, which becoems","6. Because 6+3=9, which becoem","6. Bec ause 6+3=9, which becoe","6. Because 6+3=9, which becomes 0. This makes it the inverse.","6. Because 6+3=9, which becomes 0. Th","6. Because 6+3=9, which becomes 0. T","6. Because 6+3=9, which becomes 0. ","6. Because 6+3=9, which becomes 0."],"rt":18082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":384927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odd numbers,and then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","response_history":["Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 0","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10m whi","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10m wh","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10m w","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10m ","Yes. 2 can make all the eve n number s up to 10m,","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10m","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which makes","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which make","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which mak","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which ma","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which m","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then ctone","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then cton","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then cto","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then ct","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then continues up to 9, which becomees ","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then continues up to 9, which becomees","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then continues up to 9, which be comee"," Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 aand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 andand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and mand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makeand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes and then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes thand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1  and make s theand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the and then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the oand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odd and then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odd nand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odd nuand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odd numand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 1 0, which  becomes 1 and makes the odd numberand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odd numbersand then continues up to 9, which becomes 0.","Yes. 2 can make all the even numbers up to 10, which becomes 1 and makes the odd numbers,and then continues up to 9, which becomes 0."],"rt":41184,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":426114,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. 3+3=6, 6+3=9, which becomes 0, and 0+3=3. There's no way to make the other numbers.","response_history":["No. 3+3","No. 3+","No. 3","No. 3+3=7,","No. 3+3=7","No. 3+3=6, +3=9, ","No. 3+3=6, +3=9,","No. 3+3=6, +3=9 which becm","No. 3+3=6, +3=","No. 3+3=6, +3","No. 3+3=6, +","No. 3+3=6, 6+3=9, whic ","No. 3+3=6, 6+3=9, which  becomes  0, and 0+3=3. There's no t","No. 3+3=6, 6+3=9, which becomes 0, and 0+3=3. There's no way to make the other nub","No. 3+3=6, 6+3=9, which becomes 0, and 0+3=3. There's no way to make the other numbers."],"rt":44118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":470235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, because it can make every number. 5+5=10->1, +5=6, +5=11->2, and so on.","response_history":["No, because it can't mak","No","N","Ue","U","Yes, because it can mk","Yes, because it can make every number up to an","Yes, because it can make every number up to a","Yes, because it can make every number. 5+5=10->1, +5=7","Yes, because it can make every number. 5+5=10->1, +5=6, +5=11->2, and so on."],"rt":83604,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":553841,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, it can only make 6,9,3, and 0.","response_history":["No, it can only make 6,9,3,and0","No, it can only make 6,9,3,and","No, it can only make 6,9,3,an","No, it can only make 6,9,3,a","No, it can only make 6,9,3, and 0."],"rt":30735,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":584580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":10609,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":595191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + n-1 = n","response_history":["1+Y=","1+Y","1+","1 + X = N","1 + X = n","1 + n = n","1 + n- = n","1 + n-1 = n"],"rt":48928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":644121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus the difference between x and n, will equal n.","response_history":["x + x-1 =","x + x-1 ","x + x-1","x + x-","x + x-","x + x","x + n-x = n. I","x + n-x = n. THe inverse ","x + n-x = n. THe inverse","x  + n-x =  n. THe in","x + n-x = n. THe i","x + n-x = n. THe ","x + n-x = n. THe","x + n-x = n. TH","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to he ","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to he","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to h","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the nu","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the n","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x e","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x ","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus what","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus wha","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which a dd up to  the n and become 0. So the element x, plus wh","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus wth","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus wt","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus w","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus the id","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus the i","x + n-x = n. The inverse property is two numbers which add up to the n and become 0. So the element x, plus the difference between x and n, will equal n."],"rt":48180,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":692303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know  if an el ement x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. n-1 is always a generator.","response_history":["Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The en","Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The e","Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 IGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 IsGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n  has even  generators. The generat","1 Is Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is aGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is alGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is alwGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is alwaGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is alwGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is alGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is aGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 Is Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 IsGenerators are the opposite even/odd of th e +n; so  an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 IGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 isGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is alGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is alwGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is alwaGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is alwaysGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always aGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a Gen erators  are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a gGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a genGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneatGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneatorGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneator, aGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneator, anGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators.  The gene rat","1 is always a geneator, andGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneator, and Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneator,Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneatorGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneatoGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneatGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneaGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a genearGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a geneaGenerators are the oppos ite even /odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generaGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generatGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generatoGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generatorGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, aGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, anGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generator s. The g enerat","1 is always a generator, andGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 iGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is nGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is neGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n  has even  generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is neveGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is neverGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never aGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a geGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a geneGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is al ways a g enerator, and 0 is never a generGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generaGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generatGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generatorGenerators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator.Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generat","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator m","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generato rs. The  generator is usually n-1, and any divis","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator is usually n-1, and any ","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator is usually n-1, and any","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator is usually n-1, and an","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator is usually n-1, and any divi","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator is usually n-1","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite  even/odd  of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator is","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator i","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. The generator ","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. T","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. A ","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. A ","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. A","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are  the oppo site even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. n-1 i ","1 is always a generator, and 0 is never a generator. Generators are the opposite even/odd of the +n; so an odd n has even generators. n-1 is always a generator."],"rt":212537,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":904843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["False","True"],"rt":49480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":954327,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["True","False"],"rt":16467,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":970796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":47307,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1018105,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False. For example, 4 is not a generator under +6.","response_history":["False. For example, 4 ix ","False. For example, 4 ix","False. For example, 4 is not a generator under +6."],"rt":42995,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1061103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":31765,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1092871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 (the result of x +_n x) is not. The same goes for 5 under +6 . 5 is a  generator, but 4 is not. The same also applies to 3 under +8. 3 is a generator, but 6 is not.","response_history":["0o=;'lp?_P{","Never. A number that is a generator ","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under X","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, bt","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 ( the ","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 ( the","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 ( th","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 ( t","Never. A number  that is  a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 ( ","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 (the result of x +_n x) s","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 (the result of x +_n x) is not. The same goes for 5 under +4","Never. A number that is a generator will not make a generator when applied x +_n x. For example, 7 is a generator under +8, but 6 (the result of x +_n x) is not. The same goes for 5 under +6. 5 is a generator, but 4 is not. The same also applies to 3 under +8. 3 is a generator, but 6 is not."],"rt":326254,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1419127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator  under + <sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Sometimes","Always","Sometimes","Never"],"rt":232984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1652115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1717,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1653835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"23","response_history":["23"],"rt":1918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1655754,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate h igh scho ol","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2436,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1658191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus II","response_history":["Calculus II"],"rt":9941,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1668135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what  it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1674036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":4607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1678644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned somet hing fro m this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2463,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1681108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1682932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2036,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1684970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1734,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1686705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1690808,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, on the very last question.","response_history":["Yes, on the very last question."],"rt":7446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1698255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":2423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1700680,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]